<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet Home Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org</link>
		<description>This is a .NET knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Exception Handling and Error Boundary</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-exception-handling-and-error-boundary</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how exception handling works and how to use error boundary in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Error Logging</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-error-logging</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to log error in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Dark Theme and Light Theme</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-dark-theme-and-light-theme</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to toggle dark mode and light mode in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Javascript Interop and Isolation</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-javascript-interop-and-isolation</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to interact with javascript and isolate javascript in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Styles and CSS Isolation</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-styles-and-css-isolation</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you what is CSS isolation and what factors to consider when styling your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Lazy Loading</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-lazy-loading</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to lazy load assemblies in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM App Settings</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-app-settings</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to read configuration from app settings in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Importance of Status Code in Web API</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/webapi-importance-of-status-code</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you the importance of status code in Web API. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor - SPA from ASP.NET Family</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/talks/blazor-spa-from-aspnet-family</link>
			<description>In this talk I will teach you what is blazor and why do we need to go for blazor. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Introduction</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-introduction</link>
			<description>In this post I will introduce you to Blazor WASM - Single Page Application (SPA) from ASP.NET family. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing TDD in C# .Net</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/introducing-tdd-in-csharp-dotnet</link>
			<description>In this post I will introduce you to TDD in C# .NET. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Implementing TDD in C# .Net</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/implementing-tdd-in-csharp-dotnet</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach you how to practice and implement TDD in C# .NET. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Components</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-components</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach what is components and how to use components in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Event Handling And Event Arguments</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-event-handling-and-event-arguments</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach how to handle events inside components in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Data Binding</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-data-binding</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach what is data binding and how to pass data to components in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OOPS Encapsulation</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/oops-encapsulation</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach what is encapsulation in object oriented programming. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Controlling Head Content</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-controlling-head-content</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach how to control head content in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OOPS Abstraction</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/oops-abstraction</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach what is abstraction in object oriented programming. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Communication Between Components</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-communication-between-components</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach how to communicate between components in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blazor WASM Forms</title>
			<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-forms</link>
			<description>In this post I will teach how to use forms in your Blazor applications. All with live working demo.</description>
		</item>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet Blazor Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/channels/blazor</link>
		<description>This is a .NET Blazor knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet Web API Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/channels/webapi</link>
		<description>This is a .NET Web API knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet Talk Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/channels/talk</link>
		<description>This is a .NET Talk knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet TDD Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/channels/tdd</link>
		<description>This is a .NET TDD knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet Disclaimer Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/disclaimer</link>
		<description>This is a Disclaimers for I ❤️ .Net.</description>
	</channel>

	<channel>
		<title>I ❤️ DotNet OOPS Page</title>
		<link>https://www.ilovedotnet.org/channels/oops</link>
		<description>This is a .NET OOPS knowledge sharing platform with live demos crafted by developers for developers with love.</description>
	</channel>
</rss>